{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Garage Builders","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/99975/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":99975,"taskName":"Garage - Build","taskDescription":"Build a Garage","xmTaskDescriptor":"Garage Builders","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":95,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Build building door construction builder","textMessagingName":"Build Garage","rolloverLongDesc":"Garages may be built as extensions of existing homes or as detached, stand alone structures. Often pre-fabricated sheds are built as detached garages by the manufacturer or sold as \"kits\" to be finished by the consumer or a general contractor.","rolloverShortDesc":"Professionally build attached or detached garage.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Build a Garage.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Garage Builders \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Construct or Build a Garage","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":37,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Build Garage","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Garage - Build","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Garage Builder Need","urlName":"Garage-Build","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Garage Builders - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"garage, remodel, garage door, carport","emcCategoryOid":-12036,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":782,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/99975/":{"taskOID":99975,"originalTaskOID":99975,"setID":782,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5649,"questionDisplayText":"Size of Garage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What size garage do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6046,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One car","answerDisplayText":"One car","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6048,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two car","answerDisplayText":"Two car","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6047,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three car","answerDisplayText":"Three car","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8222,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Specialty layout","answerDisplayText":"Specialty layout","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17149,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500986,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Garage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of garage do you want to build?","shortQuestionText":"What type of garage do you want to build?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6035,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Stand alone building","answerDisplayText":"Stand alone building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2311,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Extension of house or building","answerDisplayText":"Extension of house or building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17149,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5650,"questionDisplayText":"Garage Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What features do you want? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1888,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Designed to match house or building","answerDisplayText":"Designed to match house or building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2102,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Drywall","answerDisplayText":"Drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2191,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Electricity","answerDisplayText":"Electricity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5926,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Special coated flooring","answerDisplayText":"Special coated flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8224,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Extra room for storage and/or work area","answerDisplayText":"Extra room for storage and/or work area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7009,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Windows","answerDisplayText":"Windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8225,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Extra tall for special vehicles","answerDisplayText":"Extra tall for special vehicles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":898,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Automatic garage door opener","answerDisplayText":"Automatic garage door opener","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4741,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Plumbing","answerDisplayText":"Plumbing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8226,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other features","answerDisplayText":"Other features","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3304,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Insulation","answerDisplayText":"Insulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4411,"questionDisplayText":"Design Preparation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of design preparation has been done?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8431,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sketches or basic idea of project","answerDisplayText":"Sketches or basic idea of project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8430,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Architectural drawings","answerDisplayText":"Architectural drawings complete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4651,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Permits pulled","answerDisplayText":"Permits pulled","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4271,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"None","answerDisplayText":"None","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5649,"questionDisplayText":"Size of Garage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What size garage do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6046,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One car","answerDisplayText":"One car","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6048,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two car","answerDisplayText":"Two car","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6047,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three car","answerDisplayText":"Three car","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8222,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Specialty layout","answerDisplayText":"Specialty layout","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17149,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6046,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One car","answerDisplayText":"One car","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6048,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two car","answerDisplayText":"Two car","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6047,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three car","answerDisplayText":"Three car","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8222,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Specialty layout","answerDisplayText":"Specialty layout","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17149,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500986,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Garage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of garage do you want to build?","shortQuestionText":"What type of garage do you want to build?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6035,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Stand alone building","answerDisplayText":"Stand alone building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2311,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Extension of house or building","answerDisplayText":"Extension of house or building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17149,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6035,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Stand alone building","answerDisplayText":"Stand alone building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2311,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Extension of house or building","answerDisplayText":"Extension of house or building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17149,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5650,"questionDisplayText":"Garage Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What features do you want? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1888,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Designed to match house or building","answerDisplayText":"Designed to match house or building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2102,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Drywall","answerDisplayText":"Drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2191,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Electricity","answerDisplayText":"Electricity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5926,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Special coated flooring","answerDisplayText":"Special coated flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8224,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Extra room for storage and/or work area","answerDisplayText":"Extra room for storage and/or work area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7009,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Windows","answerDisplayText":"Windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8225,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Extra tall for special vehicles","answerDisplayText":"Extra tall for special vehicles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":898,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Automatic garage door opener","answerDisplayText":"Automatic garage door opener","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4741,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Plumbing","answerDisplayText":"Plumbing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8226,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other features","answerDisplayText":"Other features","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3304,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Insulation","answerDisplayText":"Insulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1888,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Designed to match house or building","answerDisplayText":"Designed to match house or building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2102,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Drywall","answerDisplayText":"Drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2191,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Electricity","answerDisplayText":"Electricity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5926,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Special coated flooring","answerDisplayText":"Special coated flooring","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8224,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Extra room for storage and/or work area","answerDisplayText":"Extra room for storage and/or work area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7009,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Windows","answerDisplayText":"Windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8225,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Extra tall for special vehicles","answerDisplayText":"Extra tall for special vehicles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":898,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Automatic garage door opener","answerDisplayText":"Automatic garage door opener","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4741,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Plumbing","answerDisplayText":"Plumbing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8226,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other features","answerDisplayText":"Other features","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3304,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Insulation","answerDisplayText":"Insulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4411,"questionDisplayText":"Design Preparation","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of design preparation has been done?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8431,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sketches or basic idea of project","answerDisplayText":"Sketches or basic idea of project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8430,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Architectural drawings","answerDisplayText":"Architectural drawings complete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4651,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Permits pulled","answerDisplayText":"Permits pulled","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4271,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"None","answerDisplayText":"None","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8431,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sketches or basic idea of project","answerDisplayText":"Sketches or basic idea of project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8430,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Architectural drawings","answerDisplayText":"Architectural drawings complete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4651,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Permits pulled","answerDisplayText":"Permits pulled","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4271,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"None","answerDisplayText":"None","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}